Lesson One.
An old man and a baby are stranded on
an island full of deadly predators.
You sail to the island to save them,
but only one person other than
you can fit on your rescue boat.
What are you gonna do?
Umm...
Oh, I get it! Okay!
I'll get off the boat and stay there!
Then the baby AND old man will fit!
That would save the boat!
No, idiot!
Wrong answer!
The old geezer's gonna die soon, anyway!
So abandon him!
Wado?
Vice Admiral, don't tell them that!
Think hard.
Why are you boys here in the first place?
Why did you join the Navy?
There's something out there
worth protecting, right?
So what is it?
All of us, all of us, dream, save us?
All of us, all of us!
of
us.
I love you.
those indentations there?
Those are fist marks from someone
using the armor of the warships as
punching bags.
Punching bags?
Do you know who did it?
Vice Admiral Garb,
starting when he was young.
He's kept it up for decades now.
It's his routine.
He's still doing it?
Why are there two of them?
The other belonged to Garb's
protege, the former admiral, Aokiji.
You can't use Haki or
devil through powers.
That's the rule of battleship bagging.
This is the strength of a true hero.
It's not something you're bored with.
And put set of flying straight to the sea!
Don't you monster!
Quick!
We gotta pull him out or he's gonna drown!
How the hell are we supposed to do that?
He beat the boss in one shot!
He can't fight this guy!
Thank you so much, Vice Admiral.
That's the legendary hero for you.
Save it, boys, I'm just getting started!
Legendary hero, my ass!
You're nothing but an old hat
who's been trashing a hideout!
And now we're gonna make
you pay for the damages!
Drive and spread fire!
Pirate! Fireballs!
Ouch! That's odd!
Stop burning me!
Are you trying to sink all island?
Calm down, you maniac!
What are we gonna do when
Commodore Teach comes back?
If he sees his face like
this, he'll kill us all!
We got garb,
outnumbered and he doesn't even flinch!
What's wrong with him?
We're in the clear!
Vice Admiral, the prisoners, our soldiers?
and all the injured have been
evacuated from the island.
They're all aboard the ship now.
Good, nice work.
Hibari, stay strong!
Watch the frozen ones, fold them slowly.
Captain, Koby, please be safe.
We're ready to set off at any time.
Okay, we're all done here, pull back!
Koby, Hababu, Bruce, come on!
Right!
On my way!
I won't miss this
hellhole, that's for sure!
This place sure lives up to the talk.
You poke a hole anywhere and these damn
pirates swarm out one after another!
I'm sorry, Garb, but like I
said, I can't let you leave.
Get ready.
I should have run, but
I still had the chance!
Oh, jeez. I'm dead.
Before we fight, I'm
your favorite too, right?
You sure you want to do this, Kuzan?
All of Blackbeard's officers
are dangerous. Be careful.
We don't have to beat them.
All we got to do is drag
our asses to the coast.
Don't let them kill you.
Yes, sir!
Somebody help me! Oh no!
I must have left one of
the prisoners behind!
I'm on my way, ma 'am!
Thank goodness we didn't
set sail without her!
Kobe, wait! Don't go!
It's a trap!
Vice Admiral Garp
Bastard!
What?
Was he invisible somehow?
Oh, sure to you.
I think Empel Down was
a better fit for you.
Whoa! Get him! Got him!
Get rid of that sword
straight through Wired Guard!
You okay, Garp?
I'll be fine!
Just get back on the ship!
This is all my fault he
got hurt defending me don't
flatter yourself Koby I
was his target all along.
Don't give up easy do you old
man it looks like garps worn
down you see any who was just
waiting to make his move?
Even normal guys like us
can take him down now.
Let's go!
All we gotta do is finish the old man off
and we'll be set for life! Hurry! Hurry!
Drop is worth as much as an animal!
He's got a free crown dowdy hat!
That's like three billion berries!
It's Kuzan!
Out of my way, Smallfrize!
Even if his hands and feet were tied
together, you still couldn't kill Garp!
Leave this to me!
Ice claw!
Hey, Garp.
I want you to mentor me.
Are you being serious?
Nah, I like my freedom.
Go bother one of the trainers.
They've taught me all they can.
I'm ready for more.
Please teach me.
I said no!
Get lost!
Ow!
Damn, that hurts.
You better not use Haki.
That won't help you learn.
I don't even know how to do that yet.
Let's do this!
What is justice to the Navy?
I don't even know anymore.
Not after a lot of time.
My son became a revolutionary!
Huh?
Damn it!
Kuzan!
What's wrong with you?
My grandson says he wants
to be a damn pirate!
What?
Why the hell would he do that?
I have no idea.
I gotta eat something.
Want to join me?
I have work to do.
Did you forget I'm an admiral? T?
Come on.
You trained a powerful enemy for yourself.
You're expelled, you dunce.
Vice-Admiral, no! No!
Garp!
Got him well after all.
Keep him safe, no matter what.
Every second you stay here,
your odds get worse and worse.
This is Pirate Island after all.
They're gonna keep coming
till you're full of lead.
You think I can't sink my claws into that
ship you've got waiting off the coast?
Allow me to demyawinstrate
the power of my Ayo-Ayo fruit.
Are you alright?
Take it slow. You're safe now.
Where is Kobe?
Please tell me he made it out. I'm sorry.
I caused you all so much trouble.
He'll be with us soon.
And you're never trouble.
Captain!
We've got trouble!
All you see in the papers is
Blackbeard this and Blackbeard that.
Well, meow, you'll see what I can do.
Let me give you a sneak preview
of tomorrow's big news story.
The famous Vice Admiral Garp led a team of
promising young elites in
an attack on Pirate Island.
They attempted to rescue Captain
Koby, the hero of the Navy.
But then the fourth ship
captain of the Blackbeard
Pirates struck and they bowed before him.
The great Avalo Pizarro
proved far too mighty.
And all of those poor brave furries
were completely annihilated.
No, please don't do this.
There are civilians on board.
Those people aren't your enemies.
Calm down, Kobe.
Mark my words, boy.
Justice will prevail.
Let's have some fun.
Blockbuster!
Don't do this.
Please let us go.
You're taking us to
Pirate Island, aren't you?
What are you going to do to us?
Didn't think Rayleigh would
stick his nose in my business,
but I got some nice
souvenirs, so who cares?
Zeh!
Vice Admiral, they're our comrades.
Can we do anything?
We're letting our men down.
We need permission from above.
Blackbeard is an emperor.
I know, but...
Zeh!
What is he doing?
Vice Admiral, Captain Koby
is with S .W .O .R .D.
S .W .O .R .D., huh?
Well, if it isn't Koby the hero, so what?
You come here to take your friends back?
If you want to start an Alto
war, that's just P .G. with me.
You're capturing 800 marines and also
commandeering one of our warships, right?
Let them go!
And you can take me instead!
You think pretty highly of
yourself, don't you, kid?
But your life is worth it.
You got a deal!
How is this even real?
It's too huge.
We can't fight that thing.
What is that?!
Open fire!
It's no use!
It isn't stopping!
We have to pull away!
Move the ship back!
Not on my watch!
They can still reach us!
Oh no!
If that hand comes down on them, hundreds
of soldiers and civilians will die!
We can't fight it!
Where would we even start?
Call everyone up to the deck!
Prepare to abandon ship!
Keep the civilians safe!
This is all my fault!
Everyone here is going
to die because of me!
I surrendered myself
to protect my comrades.
But all I've done is put
more people in danger.
I can't protect anyone!
I can't do this!
You can do it.
You can save them.
Vice Admiral Garp?
Stay calm.
I've got a plan.
I'll create an opening for you.
First, Captain Koby, you climb up to that
big rock bastard's hand and destroy it.
What?
But how can I do that?
Rear Admiral Course, when pieces of the
hand fall down, you protect the ship.
Lieutenant Commander Hamapo, don't
let anyone stand in their way.
I can try.
Vice Admiral, wait.
What if I can't...
Hesitation means defeat.
Go!
Yes, sir!
Oh, me and the others are on the move!
Give it up!
Without guard, you're all
going straight into the sea!
They're coming!
El Meppo, go get them! Huh? Why me?
Because those were your orders! Fine then!
But I don't like it!
Let's see what you've got!
That's a little garbage!
Come on, Kobe, what's the plan here?
Do you have a bomb or something?
I've got nothing.
I'll just have to play it by ear for now.
Wait, play it by ear?
You can't just play it by ear fighting
something big enough to crush a damn warship.
Trust me, I know.
Burn in hell, Kobe!
Amit?
Kobe?
Lieutenant Commander Helmepo, don't
let anyone stand in their way.
Here I go!
This...
is up to you!
Get back!
Helmepo, no!
Don't look back! Just go! But I...
You have a job to do!
I'd sit back down if I were you, Garp.
Keep moving and you'll bleed out.
This is just a scratch.
I'm trying to spare your life.
Sounds soft to me.
What are you doing here?
Wait, don't you care
what'll happen to the ship?
Galaxi Divine!
Wait! What happened?
It's pulling back!
So this is your opening, huh?
The arm went up.
What now, Kobe?
Okay, here I go!
Kobe!
Oh, now you've done it.
You think that's enough to stop me? Ha!
I'll make you pay!
Stand back and watch me do this!
I'll send your men to their graves!
And there's nothing you can do
about it! It's back! Take cover!
You can cry all you like,
but we've already won!
Hey, Almepo, Coby's making good progress,
but why the hell's he always injured?
You noticed, huh?
Oh, well, he said not to tell
you, but I guess I better.
I can't fight as well as everyone else,
even if I train ten times as much as him.
So I'll train a hundred, no,
two hundred times harder.
If that's what it takes to be a proper
marine to help people, then I'll do it!
That's enough!
Don't be stupid!
You're gonna destroy yourself!
You're telling me he's been training
by himself on top of my drills?
Yes, sir.
He's been punching the battleship
back every single night.
And he comes back with his
fists covered in blood.
Faster!
Go faster!
I HAVE TO MAKE IT IN TIME!
Is that...
Help me!
What are you doing?
Hold on, that's Koby!
Is he really trying to stop that ant?
He's gonna get crushed!
I know they call him a hero, but look!
Next to Pisano, the kid is
like the size of an ant.
Kobe, why?
Just protect yourself.
Don't worry about us. Get away. Go back.
Hey, Kobe.
You made it.
You got a front row seat to
the death of all your friends.
Even if they dive into the sea,
Aokiji will freeze them solid.
Time to take out the kitty litter.
Everyone's lives are depending on me.
I have to destroy it.
If I don't, they'll all die.
I can't fight as well as everyone else,
even if I train ten times as hard.
So I train a hundred.
Two hundred times harder!
There's something out there
worth protecting, right?
So what is it?
Kobe!
It's too late!
Abandon ship!
You can save them
I will stay in fact!
What was that?
We're saved!
No, not yet!
There's too much debris!
That's why I'm here!
Off-web!
There you go!
Kobe!
Hey!
I don't even know what to say!
That hell no, Paul.
I did it.
Yeah, you did, buddy.
You were amazing.
Look at you.
Strong enough to bring down a mountain.
Let's go home, you maniac.
Captain, help me out of my way!
Welcome back, you two!
Okay, you're alive!
Hey, body.
You're okay.
We're all going home.
Okay, once Garp is back, we'll take off.
Click.
This is Garp.
The mission to rescue
Captain Koei is a success.
Vice Admiral, you're all right.
Hurry back to the ship and we'll leave.
Actually, depart from Fulalad
immediately. That's an order.
What?
Vice Admiral, what are you talking about?
Don't you worry about this, old man.
Our top priority in this mission is
the safety of everyone on that ship.
Am I wrong?
We can't go! Hurry!
Turn the ship around!
We've won the battle today!
Our victory sends a
message to all pirates!
Please, you have to let
me join the Marines!
I'll clean and scrub and do any
chores that you'd like me to!
I'll do anything to become a Marine!
What did you boys join
the Navy to protect?
It's the future of all people, right?
You'll be part of that future, for years
to come, long after the old man's gone.
Take that baby and go.
Live your lives.
Keep going.
You all are the future of the Navy.
Don't look back!
What were you thinking?
In the future,
will you please limit the tasteless
lectures in front of the young recruits?
Why should I?
But young people's future is limitless!
The next day, newspapers reported the
heroic rescue of the Navy's young hero,
Captain Koby,
along with the sorrowful
news that Vice and Mulgarb
disappeared after his
battle on Pirate Island.
It was also reported that
the Emperor of the Sea Straw
Hat Luffy had barricaded himself
on the future island, Egghead.